# question_data = [
#     {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to "
#              "eat.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
#      "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]
question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A group of islands is called an &#039;archipelago&#039;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Israel is 7 hours ahead of New York.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it&quot; is a quote from French philosopher Voltaire.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
